I [music] don't even know why. I know.
I don't even know why I'm trying
anymore. [music]
I'm lying on my floor. Still wearing
what I wore when I [music] last saw you.
I remember when you were [music]
when you found me. Thought you would
tell me when [music] you were dreaming
of me. But now you need much more.
I know [music] you need much more.
Every day is a blue [music] sky, black
sky. Now I long for old skies. They seem
never more. [music]
Hearing thunder roar. Feeling rain.
I wonder
where [music] it all went wrong. I
remember when you were when you were a
fire me when you [music] told me when
you would drink with me. But now you
need much more.
But now you need much more.
[music]
>> [music]